Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Are you all right?
Koza! Are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you sure?
That bullet from Nanohana is still in you.
None of that matters now.
This is a battlefield we're on.
We have to stay focused
on what's happening.
Got that?
I'd like to get to one of their horses.
If we can make our way down this
street and through the center of town,
then we'll be at the North
Block where the Royal Palace is.
What are you planning, Koza?
Why go to the palace?
To reach the king and demand
that he surrender to us.
But that's insane.
The main force of the Royal Army
is stationed in the North Block,
and what's more, they're
led by Chaka and Pell.
Think of the danger.
And we haven't even managed to
gather all of our forces together.
Don't you think it would
be a better idea to wait?
Until reinforcements
arrive here to help we
can't it's already too
late for that now come on!
Wait Koza.
Holt are you aligned with the rebel army?
The only thing ahead of here in the
north block is the royal palace.
Do you understand me?
If you aren't a part of the battle
leave this area of town at once!
Hey are you listening?
This place is no playground.
You get it.
I know that.
Princess Vivi it can't
be is it really her?
Where's my father?
I need him now. Princess.
Oh never mind.
If I can't see him then take me to Chaka.
There's something that he must do.
You bastard.
That was quite a kick.
This one can compete with
my ballet kenpo moves.
You!
Out of my way!
I already told you, if you want to get
by, you'll have to defeat me first.
I hope you realize all your
efforts will be in vain.
All my life I have
practiced these dance moves.
I have perfected the dancer's
grateful art of ballet
Kenpo and it is unbeatable
even by the likes of...
Yeah!
Just give up, it's no
use trying to escape!
Ballet Kenpo!
I Degenerate Swan Death Recycle!
This dance isn't getting me anywhere!
It's time to settle this once and for all!
Col-Yay Shoot!
Hit me!
Complete!
Set!
On three!
Yeah!
Ballet get ball!
Automate shoot!
Not a pass!
My mortine chute, blocked by that clown.
My ultimate swan at a vest, stopped
by that stupid, insignificant cook.
You've got to be kidding me here.
Okay, it's time to get serious.
From now on, I mean business.
Do you hear me?
Let's see it, then.
You don't know the true extent
of my power yet, do you?
My most impressive feature is
my ability to remember faces.
Using that, I can construct and
display an incredible montage!
When you see this, you will laugh
helplessly until you collapse!
To begin, the world's
most ridiculous head!
Then the world's most ridiculous eyes!
The most ridiculous nose!
and in the world's most ridiculous mouth.
Now take a good long look,
experience the grand unveiling
of the Cape Cape Montage.
About 90 % of that was
your own ridiculous face.
I'll help you.
Stop playing dress-up, you ugly freak.
Don't you have a heart?
I'm a brilliant artist, you big jerk.
I don't have time to mess around with
your childish little tricks anymore.
Tricks, huh?
Not so fast.
They aren't just tricks.
Just wait until you see.
Within my art,
there lies the power of the greatest
friendships and the truest loves.
Right, I get it.
I see what you're planning now.
We all need love, and friends,
friends are so important.
It really just isn't
going to work, though.
Now, let's see you hurt me. No!
How could you do that?
You just attacked your little
friend with a long nose.
Well, then, clearly you don't
value friendship much, do you?
You're a real idiot.
No matter what you transform your face
to look like, you're still only you.
I'm not the kind to be fooled
by images and facades like that.
No way.
A person is their soul.
Is there a soul?
That's so... wow!
I'm so embarrassed to have been
so caught up with appearances.
I understand.
Even if I was to become...
Her, for instance, it wouldn't
make any difference to you at all.
Because images don't matter.
Well, he's easy to read.
You are such a fool!
What?
It's Vivi, it's true Princess
Vivi has come back But why now?
But princess vivi, that's insane.
We can't do something like that!
What are you afraid
would happen if we did?
But the kingdom would
simply die you're wrong.
It wouldn't this palace
is not alabasta after all
Alabasta is
It is the people who are out
there hurting each other.
They are the ones who made Alabasta
a country in the first place.
If there is any chance of stopping
this war, then we must take it.
Please, Chaka, we only need to draw
everyone's eyes over here for a few seconds.
If you can do that, then
I will take it from there.
I swear I can do this.
For now, please, destroy this palace!
But you can't be serious, Princess Vivi!
The palace has stood in the
same spot for 4,000 years!
Please don't go through with
this plan, Princess Vivi!
Chaka, you have to use your best judgment!
The king isn't even here!
You can't possibly do
this without his approval!
Sire, we must take action against the
rebels quickly before it's too late.
This is not some little quarrel.
If we strike first, they will strike back.
Are you suggesting that
we attack our citizens
before we determine who's behind all this?
Because that would be the true
destruction of our kingdom.
But we will act.
We will head out for
Rain Base and Crocodile.
Your Majesty, attacking Crocodile
now will only make things worse.
It will only add fuel to
the Rebel Army's fire.
If we leave for Rain Base now,
the Rebel Army will use our absence as
a perfect chance to attack the palace.
It doesn't matter if the Rebel Army
destroys this palace completely.
It is only a building.
You see,
even if our royal army does fall in the
end, if we can just defeat Crocodile,
this country can still be reborn as
long as its people are safe and whole.
If we battle the rebel army
instead, then that will all change.
Remember, the people are the country.
Princess Vivi!
Oh I will do as you say you're just what
they mean when they say he's nothing
but talk I bet you don't have enough
strength left to get up don't think for a
second that I'm just gonna lie down and
give up you may look like not me on the
outside but you're still the same idiot
on the inside you bastard I'll show you
I can't do it.
She's too cute.
Oh, no.
This desert air is so stifling.
It just makes me want to
rip all my clothes off.
I'll help you.
The late chop!
Ow, my eye!
That's a good one!
Kick point!
So, nothing but talk, are ya?
I'll show you talk.
Nobody messes with me.
Now, pascada.
Overing!
Eat this.
Please, don't kick me.
Oh, no.
The eyes have it.
Well, this has been a treat,
but alas, I must be off.
Duty calls and I've
got a princess to kill.
I really hate to rush things, but I'm
going to have to finish you off now.
Stand right there, lover boy,
and I'll make this quick.
Round and round and round
I go, and when I stop...
Wait a minute, did you just say we're
supposed to blow up the royal palace?
I know that it sounds crazy,
but those are the orders that
just came down from high command!
We've been ordered to blow up the palace!
They can't be serious.
That palace is 4,000 years old!
Nothing I can say can express
my sorrow at all of this.
It's alright, I know.
You really have no choice when
it comes right down to it.
It was your duty to
intercept the Rebel Army.
In spite of what happened to Igaram,
you've done well by managing to keep the
Rebellion in check for the last two years.
But I wasn't wrong.
I've met some true friends who
are going to save Alabasta.
Once the Royal Army and
the Rebel Army meet,
this country, the Kingdom of
Alabasta, will be gone forever.
However, if you truly are the one and
only hope for preventing that tragedy,
then you must survive, no matter what.
So, from this moment forward,
what happens to Luffy, or any of us for
that matter, isn't the least bit important.
All of you, who are willing to give
your lives, how are you faring now?
Princess Phoebe,
in the two years since
we've seen each other,
you've grown into a beautiful young woman.
Once this war is behind us,
all I'd like very much to hold a grand
banquet to honor your pirate friends.
Chaka, okay then?
Give me food after I beat up Crocodile.
Give me food, I'll eat till I explode.
Yes, I believe in you, Luffy.
You must be all right.
You must have defeated Crocodile?
My lord, Chaka!
Yes, report.
Is it really true that they're
going to blow up the royal palace?
The soldiers are getting explosives ready.
Surely this must be a mistake.
There's no mistake, gentlemen.
That order was given by me.
Princess Phoebe!
Use every ounce of explosives
that you can lay your hands on.
The only way to stop this
senseless fighting and to save the
lives of the people of Alabasta
is to blow up the royal palace.
What's this?
I see your weakness.
There's a flaw in your attack!
Sure enough, I was right.
You see through it.
You say through what?
What part of my ability could a
philistine like you appreciate?
Let alone see through only this?
That you can't use your precious ballet
Kenpo while you're assuming Nami's form!
It's true!
I can't bring myself to attack
you while you look like Nami.
But it's pretty clear
you have to return to
your normal self before
you try to attack me.
And it happens whenever I see you
touch your cheek with your left hand.
What?
I can't hear you!
Hey, I'm right, aren't I?
Well, so what if you all right, pal?
All right, all right,
it's only with this magnificent godlike
physique that I patiently developed,
friggin' day after day of
rigorous and brutal lessons,
that I am able to perform my ballet Kenpo.
But so what?
You're still plenty black
and blue, aren't you, Mr.
Big Talk?
Now, take a look at the
Prima of Ballet Kenpo.
I'll say this much about
it, then you're dead.
The one on your left is the pin,
and on your right is the cub.
Who cares?
Whether you see through
it or not doesn't matter.
Now, prepare to die.
Behold the power of my Ballet Kenpo!
FAMURIO!
What?
He punched a hole in the wall.
You dodged it.
Smart thinking.
At the end of the bench,
necks are still this.
He didn't even crack the
plaster around the hole.
True power, when compressed and
focused into a single point of contact,
will not destroy anything needlessly.
It might be best if you
were to try thinking of one
of my kicks like a shot
from a high-powered rifle.
Of course, in this case, the bullets
are of a drastically higher caliber.
I'm going to perforate you!
Call your...
Now go!
Damn, his reach is longer than mine.
Looks like the fight is over!
I'm flying like a swan!
Black and Poe!
Memoirs of a Winter Sky!
But the longer his reach is, the
longer it takes him to recover.
If I can avoid his kick, I'll have
that much more time to attack.
Say goodbye!
And just what do you think
you're gonna do now, lover boy?
Hey, something stuck to your
left cheek. Huh? Really?
Passo!
And drone!
Ah
Shit! Shit!
Shit!
Fire!
Fire! Generate! Call again! Shit! Shit!
Oh, my God, I'm going to kill you!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
I...
I give up.
You've got to be kidding.
You mean you're still alive?
What's the matter?
All you have to do is turn into Nami again,
and I won't be able to finish you off.
Nonsense.
I can't move with the shape I'm in.
There's no point trying to
avoid the outcome of this.
I congratulate you.
Now kill me.
You may as well.
Well, the rogue works will do it anyway.
Don't just stand there.
Get it over with.
Come on, finish me.
It was a good fight.
And beyond that, we don't
need any more words, do we?
This is without question the deep
respect that arises between rivals.
But I won't cry!
Bye now.
Oh, and I'm taking back
our sharpshooter's goggles?
Well, he did finish me.
I think I cracked a
couple of my bones again.
Everything is ready as
you ordered, Princess.
Everything is set here, too.
Hmm.
This castle has been a part of
Alabasta's history for 4,000 years.
It's been a great source of pride to me.
But if we destroy the royal palace,
the people will have to stop fighting
with each other and pay attention!
I'll finally be able to
tell everyone the truth
about this horrible
conspiracy in my own words.
Alright, light your fuses!
What is this?
You okay?
It...
was him...
We can't have this
That was rather treacherous
on your part, wasn't it?
Ah, Miss Wednesday.
After all, my dear, this
is about to be my house.
No, I'll never let you!
Your Majesty!
Father!
This is lovely, to have
a palace like this.
It's a marvelous place to look down
on all the filth and rabble below.
Where, where is Luffy?
who's that oh you mean Straw Hat that
miserable young rookie
my dear he's dead